

DOBROMIR HRISTOV

Front-end developer

dobromir92@gmail.com

+359883390558

I am a dedicated web developer, with a passion for fast, reliable, cutting edge software with over 5 years of experience.

As a front-end developer, I have been exposed to many of the rapidly evolving technologies, frameworks, bundlers, preprocessors and UI/UX trends. I adhere to popular coding practices, deliver maintainable, well-engineered products. I implement testing and automation tools for speeding up development and reliability, allowing front-end teams to focus on coding.

I enjoy writing articles, open sourcing code, authoring libraries and teaching people.

Experience

Frontend developer (remote)

Sept 2017 - Present

Hypefactors, Denmark

Web based software for PR professionals.

Started as a front end developer, solely developing and maintaining their Vue SPA blogging platform - Hype.news, later joined the development of the main Hypefactors product - a complex multilanguage Vue.js SPA with routing and shared state.

JS (ES2018, Vue.js/Vuex), Node.js, Pusher, Sass, Jest/Cypress testing, Webpack

Web Developer

Jan 2016 – Aug 2017

Welldoers, Bulgaria

Web development agency.

I worked as a web developer, mainly responsible for the development of the front-end and partially contributing to the backend. Projects included ecommerce shops of various sizes, portfolios, Facebook Apps, product websites, WordPress and Laravel API driven Apps.

 ${\sf JS}~({\sf ES2015}, {\sf Vuejs/Vuex}), {\sf Sass}, {\sf Less}, {\sf PHP}~({\sf Laravel}, {\sf WordPress})$

Web Developer

Apr 2013 - Dec 2015

STSSoft, Bulgaria

Web development agency.

Developed numerous public and private websites on various CMS and custom platforms. Worked both on front-end and back-end.

JS (jQuery), Grunt, Gulp, Brunch, Sass, PHP (Laravel, WordPress)

Education	
	
	To alamina I I Imir ra waith r Calaman a
2011-2015	Technical University Gabrovo - Bachelor's degree Computer Systems Technology

Open Source Software

Bellow is a selection of my open-source packages and contributions:

•	Palettify Configurable plugin to apply visual effects to images using their color palette
•	Vuelidate-error-extractor Easy error message display using Vuelidate validator in Vue components
•	Vue-i18n-starter A starter template to explain and ease the implementation of vue-i18n in to a Vue project.